<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<addon
  id="webinterface.default"
  version="2.2.27"
  name="Default webinterface"
  provider-name="Team-MrMC">
  <requires>
    <import addon="xbmc.json" version="6.0.0"/>
  </requires>
  <extension
    point="xbmc.webinterface"/>
  <extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
    <summary lang="af_ZA">Span MrMC Web Koppelvlak. (MrMC se verstek web koppelvlak)</summary>
    <summary lang="am_ET">የ MrMC የዌብ ገጽታዎች (የ MrMC ነባር የዌብ ገጽታዎች)</summary>
    <summary lang="ar_SA">واجهه فريق إكس بي إم سي للشبكة العنكبوتية (واجهه الشبكة العنكبوتية المبدئية لـ إكس بي إم سي)</summary>
    <summary lang="be_BY">Team-MrMC Web Interface. (MrMC's default web interface)</summary>
    <summary lang="bg_BG">Уеб интерфейс на Team-MrMC. (стандартният уеб интерфейс на MrMC)</summary>
    <summary lang="ca_ES">Interfície web de l'equip MrMC. (la interfície web per defecte del MrMC)</summary>
    <summary lang="cs_CZ">Webové rozhraní týmu MrMC (Výchozí webové rozhraní MrMC).</summary>
    <summary lang="cy_GB">Rhyngwyneb Gwe Team-MrMC (Rhyngwyneb gwe rhagosodedig MrMC)</summary>
    <summary lang="da_DK">Team-MrMC Web-grænseflade. (MrMC's standard webgrænseflade)</summary>
    <summary lang="de_DE">Team-MrMC Webinterface. (Standardwebinterface von MrMC)</summary>
    <summary lang="el_GR">Διεπαφή Ιστού της Team-MrMC. (Προεπιλεγμένη διεπαφή ιστού του MrMC)</summary>
    <summary lang="en_AU">Team-MrMC Web Interface. (MrMC's default web interface)</summary>
    <summary lang="en_GB">Team-MrMC Web Interface. (MrMC's default web interface)</summary>
    <summary lang="en_NZ">Team-MrMC Web Interface. (MrMC's default web interface)</summary>
    <summary lang="en_US">Team-MrMC Web Interface. (MrMC's default web interface)</summary>
    <summary lang="es_AR">Interfaz Web del Equipo de MrMC. (Interfaz web por defecto de MrMC)</summary>
    <summary lang="es_ES">Interfaz web de MrMC. (Interfaz web por defecto de MrMC)</summary>
    <summary lang="es_MX">Interfaz Web del Equipo de MrMC (Interfaz Web por defecto de MrMC)</summary>
    <summary lang="et_EE">MrMC meeskonna veebikeskkond. (Vaikimisi keskkond)</summary>
    <summary lang="eu_ES">MrMC taldean Web Interfazea. (MrMC-ren lehenetsiriko web interfazea)</summary>
    <summary lang="fa_AF">نمایه وب تیم MrMC.(رابط پیش فرض MrMC)</summary>
    <summary lang="fa_IR">رابط وب تیم MrMC. (رابط وب استاندارد MrMC)</summary>
    <summary lang="fi_FI">Team-MrMC:n WWW-käyttöliittymä. (MrMC:n oletus WWW-käyttöliittymä)</summary>
    <summary lang="fr_CA">Interface Web de l'équipe-MrMC. (Interface Web par défaut d'MrMC)</summary>
    <summary lang="fr_FR">Interface internet de l'Équipe-MrMC. (Interface internet par défaut de MrMC)</summary>
    <summary lang="gl_ES">Interface web da equipa de MrMC. (Interface web predefinida de MrMC)</summary>
    <summary lang="he_IL">ממשק הדפדפן הרשמי של MrMC. (ברירת המחדל)</summary>
    <summary lang="hr_HR">Tim MrMC Web sučelje. (MrMCjevo uobičajeno web sučelje)</summary>
    <summary lang="hu_HU">Az MrMC csapat Webes kezelőfelülete (MrMC alapértelmezett webes kezelőfelülete)</summary>
    <summary lang="id_ID">Antar Muka Web Tim MrMC. (Antar muka web bawaan MrMC)</summary>
    <summary lang="is_IS">Team-MrMC Vefviðmót. (Sjálfgefið vefviðmót á MrMC)</summary>
    <summary lang="it_IT">Interfaccia Web del Team-MrMC. (Interfaccia web di default per MrMC)</summary>
    <summary lang="ja_JP">Team-MrMC Web Interface. (MrMC's default web interface)</summary>
    <summary lang="ko_KR">Team-MrMC 웹 인터페이스. (MrMC 기본 웹 인터페이스)</summary>
    <summary lang="lt_LT">Komandos MrMC Web sąsaja.(MrMC numatytoji žiniatinklio sąsaja)</summary>
    <summary lang="lv_LV">Team-MrMC tīmekļa saskarne. (MrMC noklusētā tīmekļa saskarne)</summary>
    <summary lang="mk_MK">Веб интерфејс на  MrMC тимот. (MrMC's подразбирачки веб интерфејс)</summary>
    <summary lang="ms_MY">Antaramuka Sesawang Pasukan-MrMC (antaramuka sesawang lalai MrMC) </summary>
    <summary lang="mt_MT">Web interface ta' Team-MrMC.  (Il-Web interface normali ta' MrMC)</summary>
    <summary lang="my_MM">Team-MrMC ဝက်ဘ် အသွင်အပြင် (MrMC ၏ မူရင် ဝက်ဘ် အသွင်အပြင်)</summary>
    <summary lang="nb_NO">Team-MrMC nettgrensesnitt. (MrMCs standard nettgrensesnitt)</summary>
    <summary lang="nl_NL">Team-MrMC Webinterface. (MrMC's standaard webinterface)</summary>
    <summary lang="pl_PL">Interfejs webowy MrMC. (Domyślny)</summary>
    <summary lang="pt_BR">Interface Web da Equipe MrMC. (interface web padrão do MrMC)</summary>
    <summary lang="pt_PT">Interface web da Team-MrMC. (Interface web padrão do MrMC)</summary>
    <summary lang="ro_RO">Interfață web MrMC. (interfață web implicită pentru MrMC)</summary>
    <summary lang="ru_RU">Веб-интерфейс от разработчиков MrMC (веб-интерфейс MrMC по умолчанию).</summary>
    <summary lang="sk_SK">Webové rozhranie tímu MrMC. (predvolené webové rozhranie pre MrMC)</summary>
    <summary lang="sl_SI">Spletni vmesnik ekipe MrMC. (Privzet spletni vmesnik za MrMC)</summary>
    <summary lang="sr_RS">Web интерфејс MrMC Тима (подразуевани web интерфејс MrMC-jа)</summary>
    <summary lang="sr_RS@latin">Web interfejs MrMC Tima (podrazuevani web interfejs MrMCja)</summary>
    <summary lang="sv_SE">Team-MrMC webbgränsnitt. (MrMC's standardwebbgränssnitt)</summary>
    <summary lang="szl">Webowy interfejs ôd Team-MrMC (wychodny webowy interface we MrMC).</summary>
    <summary lang="ta_IN">கோடி குழுமத்தின் இணைய இடைமுகம். (கோடியின் நிரந்தர இணைய இடைமுகம்)</summary>
    <summary lang="te_IN">టీమ్-కోడి వెబ్ ఇంటర్ఫేస్. (కోడి యొక్క డిఫాల్ట్ వెబ్ ఇంటర్ఫేస్)</summary>
    <summary lang="tg_TJ">Интерфейси веби гурӯҳи кории MrMC Web. (Интерфейси веби пешфарз барои MrMC)</summary>
    <summary lang="th_TH">ทีมส่วนประสานหน้าเว็บ MrMC (ส่วนประสานหน้าเว็บพื้นฐานของ MrMC)</summary>
    <summary lang="tr_TR">MrMC Takımı Web Arayüzü. (MrMC'nin varsayılan web arayüzü)</summary>
    <summary lang="uk_UA">Веб-інтерфейс MrMC (Типовий веб-інтерфейс  для MrMC)</summary>
    <summary lang="uz_UZ">MrMC guruhi veb Interfeysi. (MrMC andoza veb interfeysi)</summary>
    <summary lang="vi_VN">Đội ngũ giao diện Web MrMC. (Giao diện Web mặc định của MrMC)</summary>
    <summary lang="zh_CN">MrMC 团队开发的 Web 界面。（MrMC 的默认 web 界面）</summary>
    <summary lang="zh_TW">MrMC團隊網頁介面。(MrMC的預設網頁介面)</summary>
    <description lang="af_ZA">Verstek web koppelvlak vir MrMC; Ontwerp vir toestelle van alle resolusies</description>
    <description lang="am_ET">ነባር የዌብ ገጽታዎች ለ MrMC ፡ የተነደፈው ለሁሉም አካላቶች resolutions ነው </description>
    <description lang="ar_SA">واجهه الشبكة العنكبوتية المبدئية لـ إكس بي إم سي، مُصمَمة لتناسب كافة قياسات أبعاد الشاشات</description>
    <description lang="be_BY">Стандартны вэб-інтэрфэйс да MrMC; распрацаваны для прыладаў зь любымі разрознасьцямі</description>
    <description lang="bg_BG">Стандартния уеб интерфейс на MrMC; Направен е за устройства с най-различни резолюции</description>
    <description lang="ca_ES">Interfície web per defecte del MrMC; Dissenyada per dispositius de totes les resolucions</description>
    <description lang="cs_CZ">Výchozí webové rozhraní MrMC navržené pro zařízení s libovolným rozlišením</description>
    <description lang="cy_GB">Rhyngwyneb gwe rhagosodedig MrMC. Wedi ei gynllunio ar gyfer cydraniad pob dyfais</description>
    <description lang="da_DK">Standard webgrænseflade til MrMC; designet til enheder i alle opløsninger</description>
    <description lang="de_DE">Standard MrMC Webinterface - Für alle Geräte und Auflösungen geeignet</description>
    <description lang="el_GR">Προεπιλεγμένη διεπαφή ιστού για το MrMC. Σχεδιασμένη για συσκευές όλων των αναλύσεων.</description>
    <description lang="en_AU">Default web interface for MrMC; Designed for devices of all resolutions</description>
    <description lang="en_GB">Default web interface for MrMC; Designed for devices of all resolutions</description>
    <description lang="en_NZ">Default web interface for MrMC; Designed for devices of all resolutions</description>
    <description lang="en_US">Default web interface for MrMC; Designed for devices of all resolutions</description>
    <description lang="es_AR">Interfaz web por defecto de MrMC. Diseñada para dispositivos de cualquier resolución</description>
    <description lang="es_ES">Interfaz web por defecto de MrMC. Diseñada para dispositivos de cualquier resolución</description>
    <description lang="es_MX">Interfaz Web por defecto para MrMC; Diseñado para dispositivos de todas las resoluciones</description>
    <description lang="et_EE">MrMC vaikimisi veebikeskkond; Disainitud erinevate resolutsioonidega seadmetele.</description>
    <description lang="eu_ES">MrMC-ren lehenetsiriko web interfazea. Erresoluzio guztietako gailentzat diseinatua</description>
    <description lang="fa_AF">رابط پیش فرض MrMCوطراحی شده برای هر رزولیشن</description>
    <description lang="fa_IR">رابط استاندارد وب برای MrMC. قابل استفاده برای همه دستگاه ها و همه رزولوشن ها</description>
    <description lang="fi_FI">Oletus WWW-käyttöliittymä MrMC:lle. Suunniteltu käytettäväksi kaiken kokoisilla laitteilla.</description>
    <description lang="fr_CA">Interface Web par défaut d'MrMC - Conçue pour les dispositifs de toutes résolutions</description>
    <description lang="fr_FR">Interface internet par défaut de MrMC ; adaptée aux appareils de toutes résolutions</description>
    <description lang="gl_ES">Interface web predefinida para MrMC, deseñada para dispositivos de todas as resolucións</description>
    <description lang="he_IL">ממשק דפדפן ברירת המחדל עבור MrMC; מותאם למכשירים בעלי אבחנות שונות</description>
    <description lang="hr_HR">Uobičajeno web sučelje za MrMC; Dizajnirano za uređaje svih razlučivosti</description>
    <description lang="hu_HU">Az MrMC alapértelmezett webes kezelőfelülete; Minden felbontásra alkalmas</description>
    <description lang="hy_AM">Նախնական տեսք MrMC-ի համար; Նախատեսված է բոլոր կրիչների համար</description>
    <description lang="id_ID">Antar muka web bawaan bagi MrMC; Dirancang untuk perangkat dengan semua resolusi</description>
    <description lang="is_IS">Sjálfgefið vefviðmót fyrir MrMC; Hannað fyrir tæki með allskonar upplausnir</description>
    <description lang="it_IT">Interfaccia Web di default per MrMC; Realizzata per periferiche con qualunque risoluzione</description>
    <description lang="ja_JP">MrMC のデフォルト Web インターフェースです。さまざまな解像度のデバイス用にデザインされています。</description>
    <description lang="ko_KR">MrMC 기본 웹 인터페이스; 모든 해상도의 기기를 위해 디자인 됨</description>
    <description lang="lt_LT">Numatytoji MrMC Web sąsaja skirta visų rezoliucijų prietaisams</description>
    <description lang="lv_LV">Noklusētā MrMC tīmekļa sakarne; Piemērota visu izšķirtspēju iekārtām</description>
    <description lang="mk_MK">Подразбирачки веб интерфејс за MrMC; Дизајниран за уреди со сите резолуции</description>
    <description lang="ms_MY">Antaramuka sesawang lalai untuk MrMC; Direka untuk peranti pelbagai resolusi</description>
    <description lang="mt_MT">Il-Web interface in-normali ta' MrMC; Iddiżinjata għal apparat ta' kull reżoluzzjoni</description>
    <description lang="my_MM">MrMC အတွက် မူရင်း ဝက်ဘ် အသွင်ပြင် ၊ စက်များ အားလုံး၏ resolutions အတွက် ရေးဆွဲထားသည်။</description>
    <description lang="nb_NO">Standard nettgrensesnitt for MrMC; Laget for alle oppløsninger</description>
    <description lang="nl_NL">Standaard MrMC-webinterface; geschikt voor alle resoluties</description>
    <description lang="pl_PL">Domyślny interfejs webowy MrMC; Zaprojektowany dla urządzeń o ekranach w dowolnej rozdzielczości</description>
    <description lang="pt_BR">Interface web padrão para MrMC; Concebida para dispositivos de todas as resoluções</description>
    <description lang="pt_PT">Interface web padrão do MrMC. Criada para dispositivos de todas as resoluções.</description>
    <description lang="ro_RO">Interfață web implicită pentru MrMC, realizată de echipa MrMC pentru dispozitive cu orice rezoluție.</description>
    <description lang="ru_RU">Веб-интерфейс MrMC по умолчанию. Разработан для устройств с любыми разрешениями.</description>
    <description lang="si_LK">MrMC' සඳහා නියත  වෙබ් අතුරුමුහුණත; සෑම විභේදනයකම උපකරණ සඳහා නිර්මාණය කර ඇත</description>
    <description lang="sk_SK">Predvolené webové rozhranie pre MrMC; Navrhnuté pre zariadenia zobrazujúce v akomkoľvek rozlíšení</description>
    <description lang="sl_SI">Privzet spletni vmesnik za MrMC, ustvarjen za naprave vseh ločljivosti</description>
    <description lang="sr_RS">Подразумевани web интерфејс MrMC; Намењен уређајима свих резолуција</description>
    <description lang="sr_RS@latin">Podrazumevani web interfejs MrMC; Namenjen uređajima svih rezolucija</description>
    <description lang="sv_SE">Standardwebbgränssnitt för MrMC; Utformat för alla enheter oavsett skärmupplösning</description>
    <description lang="szl">Wychodny webowy interface we MrMC. Zrychtowany dlŏ maszin we wszyjskich rozdziylczościach.</description>
    <description lang="ta_IN">கோடி இற்கான நிரந்தர இணைய இடைமுகம்; சகல சாதனங்களின் திரைகளுக்கும் வடிவமைக்கப்பட்டது</description>
    <description lang="te_IN">కోడి డిఫాల్ట్ వెబ్ ఇంటర్ఫేస్; అన్ని వైశాల్యాలు పరికరాల కోసం రూపొందించబడింది</description>
    <description lang="tg_TJ">Интерфейси веби пешфарз барои MrMC; Барои ҳар гуна дастгоҳ бо возеҳии экранаш гуногун эҷод карда шудааст</description>
    <description lang="th_TH">ส่วนประสานหน้าเว็บพื้นฐานสำหรับ MrMC ได้ออกแบบรองรับความละเอียดหน้าจอของอุปกรณ์ทั้งหมด</description>
    <description lang="tr_TR">MrMC için varsayılan web arayüzü; Bütün çözünürlüklerde tüm cihazlar için dizayn edilmiştir.</description>
    <description lang="uk_UA">Типовий веб-інтерфейс  для MrMC; Розроблений для пристроїв з будь-якою роздільною здатністю</description>
    <description lang="uz_UZ">MrMC uchun andoza veb interfeysi; barcha ekran o'lchamlari bilan uskunalar uchun yaratilgan</description>
    <description lang="vi_VN">Giao diện Web mặc định cho MrMC; Thiết kế cho các thiết bị ở tất cả độ phân giải khác nhau</description>
    <description lang="zh_CN">MrMC 的默认 web 界面；为支持所有分辨率的设备而设计</description>
    <description lang="zh_TW">MrMC的預設網頁介面；針對所有解析度的設備而設計</description>
    <platform>all</platform>
  </extension>
</addon>
