<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<addon
  id="skin.pm3-hd"
  version="2.5.0"
  name="PM3.HD4MrMC"
  provider-name="Jezz_X, Team XBMC, BAG_Ass">
  <requires>
    <import addon="xbmc.gui" version="5.3.1"/>
  </requires>
  <extension
    point="xbmc.gui.skin"
    defaultthemename="Textures.xbt"
    debugging="false"
    effectslowdown="1.0">
    <res width="1280" height="720" aspect="16:9" default="true" folder="720p" />
  </extension>
  <extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
    <summary lang="ru">PM3.HD тема созданная Jezz_X с исправлениями BAG_Ass</summary>
    <summary lang="de">Project Mayhem III High Definition skin by Jezz_X</summary>
    <summary lang="el">Το κέλυφος Project Mayhem III High Definition από τον Jezz_X</summary>
    <summary lang="en">Project Mayhem III High Definition skin by Jezz_X</summary>
    <summary lang="es">Project Mayhem III High Definition skin por Jezz_X</summary>
    <summary lang="fa_IR">Project Mayhem III پوسته ی HD توسط Jezz_X</summary>
    <summary lang="hu">PM3.HD skin (szerző: Jezz_X)</summary>
    <summary lang="nl">PM3.HD skin door Jezz_X</summary>
    <summary lang="pl">Projekt Mayhem III HD skóra autorstwa Jezz_X</summary>
    <summary lang="pt">Tema 'Project Mayhem III High Definition', desenvolvido por Jezz_X</summary>
    <summary lang="pt_BR">Project Mayhem III High Definition skin por Jezz_X</summary>
    <description lang="ru">PM3.HD (Project Mayhem III High Definition)</description>
    <description lang="de">PM3.HD (Project Mayhem III High Definition) basiert auf dem Design des alten Standardskins Project Mayhem III von Chokemaniac.[CR][CR]Dieses Skin wurde erstellt als XBMC von der xbox Platform auf PC's überging.   Menschen wollten XBMC auf HD TVs in 720p und 1080p nutzen und es viel mir auf, dass das alte Standardskin Project Mayhem III auf der niedrigen Auflösung der xbox gut aussah, in HD aber pixelig war.   Also wurde PM3.HD erstellt, um die Lücke mit unserer ersten "stable" Veröffentlichung für Linux, OSX und Windows für HD Nutzer zu schließen.</description>
    <description lang="el">Το PM3.HD (Project Mayhem III High Definition) βασίστηκε στο σχεδιασμό του παλαιότερου κελύφους Project Mayhem III από τον Chokemaniac.[CR][CR]Αυτό το κέλυφος δημιουργήθηκε κατά τη μεταφορά του XBMC από την παιχνιδομηχανή xbox στον Η/Υ.   Καθώς ο κόσμος ήθελε να χρησιμοποιήσει το XBMC στις Υψηλής Ευκρίνειας τηλεοράσεις τους σε αναλύσεις 720p και 1080p, και διαπίστωσα ότι το παλιό κέλυφος Project Mayhem III ακόμα έδειχνε καλό στο χαμηλής ανάλυσης xbox, αλλά η ποιότητα της εικόνας χαλούσε σε υψηλή ανάλυση.    Έτσι δημιουργήθηκε το PM3.HD, προκειμένου να γεμίσει το κενό για χρήστες Υψηλής Ευκρίνειας τηλεοράσεων με την πρώτη επίσημη "σταθερή" έκδοση του XBMC για Linux, OSX και Windows.</description>
    <description lang="en">PM3.HD (Project Mayhem III High Definition) was based on the design of the old default skin Project Mayhem III by Chokemaniac.[CR][CR]This skin was created as XBMC moved off the xbox platform onto PC's.   People were wanting to use XBMC on High Definition TV in 720p and 1080p and it came to my attention that the old default Project Mayhem III skin looked great on the low resolution xbox but looked very blocky when scaled up to Hi definition.    So PM3.HD was created to fill the gap for High definition users with our first official "stable" release of XBMC for Linux, OSX and Windows.</description>
    <description lang="fa_IR">PM3.HD (Project Mayhem III با کیفیت بسیار بالا)  در طراحی بر اساس پروژه قدیمی پوسته Project Mayhem III توسط Chokemaniac است. [CR] [CR] این پوست وقتی ساخته شد که XBMC در خارج از پلت فرم ایکس باکس بر روی کامپیوتر نقل مکان کرد. مردم مایل به استفاده از XBMC در تلویزیون با کیفیت بالای 720P و 1080P بوده و من متوجه شدم که پوسته ی قدیمی Project Mayhem III  در رزولوشن پایین بسیار عالی است، اما وقتی به رزولیشن  HD تغییر اندازه دهیم تصاویر خیلی بلوکه شده به نظر می رسد. بنابراین PM3.HD برای پر کردن شکاف برای کاربران HD با اولین ریلیز  "پایدار" از XBMC لینوکس و برای سیستم عامل های لینوکس، OSX و ویندوز ساخته شده است.</description>
    <description lang="hu">PM3.HD (Project Mayhem III High Definition) egy régi alapskinre épül (Project Mayhem III, szerző: Chokemaniac).[CR][CR]Ez a skin akkor keletkezett amikor az XBMC átváltott a PC platforma, amikor a felhasználók a nagyfelbontású (720p, 1080p) TV készülékeiken akarták élvezni az XBMC-t. Ez volt az alapskin az első "hivatalos" stabil verzióban a Linux, Windows és OSX platformokon.</description>
    <description lang="nl">PM3.HD (Project Mayhem III High Definition) is gebaseerd op het design van de oude standaard skin (PM3) door Chokemaniac.[CR]  Deze skin werd ontworpen toen XBMC van het xbox platform naar PC's verhuisde. Mensen wilden toen XBMC gebruiken op HD TVs in 720p en 1080p en de originele PM3 skin werd slecht weergegeven in deze hoge resoluties. Dit lag aan de de basis van de PM3.HD skin</description>
    <description lang="pt">O tema PM3.HD (Project Mayhem III High Definition) foi baseado no desenho do velho tema padrão do XBMC, 'Project Mayhem III', desenvolvido por Chokemaniac.[CR][CR]Este tema foi criado quando o XBMC deixou de ser desenvolvido para a plataforma xbox.   A comunidade queria usar o XBMC em TVs de alta-definição (720p and 1080p) e chamou à atenção para o facto que o velho tema 'Project Mayhem III' era visualmente agradável na xbox, mas ficava horrível quando usado em aparelhos capazes de alta-definição.    Assim, o tema PM3.HD foi criado para preencher o vazio existente que os utilizadores notaram na primeira versão estável para Linux, OSX e Windows, plataformas já com capacidade para alta-definição.</description>
    <description lang="pt_BR">PM3.HD (Project Mayhem III High Definition)é baseado no design de antiga  skin Project Mayhem III por Chokemaniac.[CR][CR]Esta skin foi criada quando moveu-se da plataforma xbox para PC's. Pessoas estavam querendo usar o XBMC na TV de alta definição em 720p e 1080p e ele veio ao meu conhecimento que o velho padrão da skin Project Mayhem III parecia perfeita em baixa resolução no xbox, mas parecia muito blocky quando ampliadas para alta definição. Então PM3.HD foi criado para preencher a lacuna para usuários de alta definição.</description>
    <platform>all</platform>
  </extension>
</addon>
