<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8' standalone='yes'?>
<addon id="skin.sio2" version="3.9.0" name="SiO2" provider-name="FastColors">
  <requires>
    <import addon="xbmc.gui" version="5.10.0"/>
    <!-- <import addon="script.favourites" version="3.2.5"/> -->
    <!-- <import addon="service.library.data.provider" version="0.0.4"/> -->
  </requires>
  <extension point="xbmc.gui.skin" defaultthemename="Textures.xbt" effectslowdown="1" debugging="false">
        <res width="1920" height="1080" aspect="16:9" default="true" folder="1080i"/>
    </extension>
  <extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
    <platform>all</platform>
	<summary lang="ar">A simple and handy Skin visually based on AppleTv</summary>
    <summary lang="be">A simple and handy Skin visually based on AppleTv</summary>
    <summary lang="bg">A simple and handy Skin visually based on AppleTv</summary>
    <summary lang="ca">Una Skin simple i pràctic basat en AppleTV</summary>
    <summary lang="cs">Jednoduchý a praktický kůže na základě AppleTV</summary>
    <summary lang="da">En enkel og handy Skin baseret på AppleTV</summary>
    <summary lang="de">Eine einfache und handliche Skin on AppleTv Basis</summary>
    <summary lang="el">Ένα απλό και εύχρηστο δέρματος με βάση AppleTV</summary>
    <summary lang="en">A simple and handy visually Skin based on AppleTv</summary>
    <summary lang="es">Una Skin simple y práctica basada en AppleTv</summary>
    <summary lang="et">Lihtne ja mugav Naha põhineb AppleTV</summary>
    <summary lang="fi">Yksinkertainen ja kätevä Skin perustuvat AppleTV</summary>
    <summary lang="fr">Une Skin simple et pratique basée sur AppleTv</summary>
    <summary lang="gl">A pel simple e accesible con base na AppleTV</summary>
    <summary lang="he">עור פשוט ושימושי המבוסס על AppleTV</summary>
    <summary lang="hr">Jednostavan i praktičan Skin temelji se na AppleTV</summary>
    <summary lang="hu">Egy egyszerű és praktikus Skin alapuló AppleTV</summary>
    <summary lang="is">A einfaldur og vel Skin byggir á AppleTv</summary>
    <summary lang="it">Una Skin semplice e pratica basata su AppleTV</summary>
    <summary lang="ja">AppleTVのに基づいて、シンプルかつ便利なスキン</summary>
    <summary lang="km">A simple and handy Skin visually based on AppleTv</summary>
    <summary lang="ko">AppleTV에서 기반 간단하고 편리 스킨</summary>
    <summary lang="lt">Paprasta ir patogu Skin remiantis AppleTV</summary>
    <summary lang="mk">A simple and handy Skin visually based on AppleTv</summary>
    <summary lang="nl">Een eenvoudige en handige Skin op basis van AppleTV</summary>
    <summary lang="no">En enkel og praktisk Skin basert på AppleTV</summary>
    <summary lang="pl">Proste i wygodne skóry oparta na AppleTV</summary>
    <summary lang="pt">A Skin simples e acessível com base na AppleTV</summary>
    <summary lang="ro">O piele simplă și la îndemână pe AppleTV</summary>
    <summary lang="ru">Простая и удобная кожи основана на AppleTV</summary>
    <summary lang="sk">Jednoduchý a praktický kože na základe AppleTV</summary>
    <summary lang="sl">Preprost in priročen kože temelji na AppleTV</summary>
    <summary lang="sv">En enkel och praktisk hud baserad på AppleTV</summary>
    <summary lang="th">ผิวที่เรียบง่ายและมีประโยชน์จาก AppleTV</summary>
    <summary lang="tr">AppleTV dayanan basit ve kullanışlı Cilt</summary>
    <summary lang="uk">Проста і зручна шкіри заснована на AppleTV</summary>
    <summary lang="vi">Giao diện đơn giản và tiện dụng dựa trên AppleTV</summary>
    <summary lang="zh">一个简单和方便的皮肤上的AppleTV</summary>
    

    <description lang="en">If you like Apple "everything at hand" policy for interfaces, You might want to give this Skin a try. I designed it trying to put as few clicks as possible between You and what You're trying to do (or watch ;) ).[CR]Thanks to Pecinko for Quartz as a solid base to build on.[CR] Thanks to testers and Inspirers: Toiva, Scrolling, Abrasher, Lucanoid, Relyter.</description>
    <description lang="it">Se ti piace la politica di Apple per le interfacce grafiche "tutto a portata di mano", allora dovresti provare questa Skin. L'ho progettata cercando di mettere il minor numero di click tra te e quello che stai cercando di fare (o di guardare ;) ).[CR]Grazie a Pecinko per Quartz come solida base di partenza.[CR] Grazie ai testers e agli ispiratori:.. Toiva, Scrolling, Abrasher, Lucanoid, Relyter.</description>

    <disclaimer>SiO2 - Enjoy</disclaimer>
  </extension>
</addon>
